

# Ghazal Yoonesi

### About Me

As a UX/UI enthusiast with a background in language education, photography, and sales, I am advancing my skills in UX/UI design through education with Career Foundry. With experience in customer-facing roles, including seller, teaching and photography, I excel at delivering impactful solutions to clients and users.

### Personal Data

Name: Ghazal Yoonesi

E-mail: yoonesi.ghazal@gmail.com

### IT-Skills

Figma: Expert

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Lightroom: Proficient

MS-Office: Beginner

## Job Experience

From 09/2022 Seller - Bakery Lange, Paderborn

- Managing the entire branch effectively during peak times.
- Acknowledged and welcomed clients, overseeing daily operations.
- o Fostered the branch with 7 tables accommodating up to 20 customers, ensuring timely service and consistently greeting customers with a smile.

01/2021-12/2021 Self employed Photographer (Realstate), LemonOne

- Capturing appealing house photos for LemonOne's real estate listings.
- Applied photography expertise and editing skills to highlight property features effectively.
- o Enhanced listing attractiveness, attracting more buyers and boosting LemonOne's reputation for top-tier visual content in real estate.

09/2017-03/2018 English Teacher for children, Iran Mehr Institute, Tehran, Iran

- Teaching English to 30 primary school students of varying proficiency.
- Used fluent English and interactive teaching methods (games, storytelling) with enthusiasm.
- Increased student engagement, higher test scores, and positive feedback, fostering improved English skills and a supportive classroom atmosphere.

### Education

From 03/2023 UX/UI, Career Foundry, Berlin - online

06/2019-03/2022 Deutsch Intensiv Kurse (DSH), Paderborn University

09/2015-09/2017 English Intensive Course, Respina Talk, Tehran, Iran

09/2012-09/2017 Bachelor of Arts in Script Writing, Islamic Azad University Of Central Tehran Branch, Tehran, Iran (15.19/20)

2008-2011 High School Diploma (Field: Graphic), Modares Technical High School, Tehran, Iran (15.33/20)

## Languages

English: Nivea C1 German: Nivea C1

Persian: Mother tongue

## Hobbies

Travel, Cycling, Cooking, Board games, Music, Movies